她们有枪
They have guns.
许多枪
A lot of them.
我看见了
I saw it.
什么
What?
那个团体
That group.
我遇见的女人们
Um, the women I met.
她们有武器库 有枪
They have an armory. They have guns.
你之前怎么不跟我们说
Why didn't you tell us before now?
我做过保证 瑞克
I made a promise, Rick.
你会想起你杀掉的人吗
Do you ever think about who you've killed?
会
Yeah.
如果计划失败 你准备好了吗
Are you ready if this goes south?
不会失败的
It won't.
如果失败了 你不必内疚
If it does, you don't need to feel bad.
我的确内疚
I do feel bad.
我会内疚的
I will.
塔拉
Tara...
你不必
you don't have to.
《行尸走肉》
你得用一块防水布盖住
You need to cover this with a tarp.
- 防水布吗  - 对
A tarp? Tarp.
为什么
Why?
你想想
Think about it.
直接告诉我吧
Okay. Just tell me.
我们需要保温
We want warmth
这样它们就会在冬天来临之前发芽
so they'll put out shoots before the fast freeze.
那样的话 我们扯掉防水布
That way, we pull back the tarp,
它们就会自然死亡
they die naturally,
就不用一直除草了
saves on all the endless weeding.
去盖防水布吧
Get to tarping.
没问题 女老大
You got it, boss lady.
等等 你去哪里
Uh, wait. Where are you going?
我不是农民
I, uh -- I'm not a farmer.
我需要帮助
I need some help here.
你不需要
No, you don't.
我看见外面生长着野生蓝莓灌木丛
I saw a wild blueberry bush growing outside.
如果足够嫩
If it's young enough,
我就要把它拔出来种在这里
I'm gonna pull it up and replant it here.
好植株能结40多年的蓝莓
Good one will produce for over 40 years.
我们得开始规划活那么久了
We got to start acting like we'll be around that long.
挺好的
Cool. Yeah.
就盖防水布 别碰
Just tarp. Don't touch.
之后我来看看你做得怎么样
I'll see how you do after.
你上去后 注意信号
Once you're up, watch for the signal.
几点开始
What time does the clock start?
等她一进去就开始
Soon as she's in.
你没事吧
You good?
我很好
I'm good enough.
很高兴你来了 我知道这很艰难
I'm glad you came. I know it's been hard.
- 我知道你不想这样  - 我之前不想
I know you don't want this. Didn't want this,
但我现在开始明白是怎么回事了
but I'm starting to understand what's on the menu now.
我们可以像这些人一样躲藏
We can hide like these people,
我们可以继续供奉救世军
we can keep trying to serve The Saviors,
我可以时常看见你被毒打
and I can watch you get randomly beaten every so often,
或者我们可以反抗
or else we can fight.
所以我们来了
So, here we are.
而且跟你在一起
And being with you, well...
让无助的恐惧可以容忍了
it makes abject terror tolerable.
我该更努力地阻止罗西塔和萨沙的
I should've tried harder to stop Rosita and Sasha.
如果她们再等我一天
If they'd have just waited one more day...
萨沙枪法很好
Well, Sasha's a good shot,
罗西塔知道如何照顾自己
and Rosita knows how to take care of herself.
她们也许现在都回山顶寨了
Probably back at Hilltop right now.
至少我希望如此 我们需要她们
Least I hope so. We're gonna need 'em.
还得死很多人的
There's a whole lot of people still got to die.
你好啊
Hey, there.
没事吧
You okay?
能给我点水喝吗
Can I get some water?
我该自我介绍一下
I should introduce myself.
我是大卫
I'm David.
不知道你昨晚是否记得我
I wonder if you remember me from last night.
你记得吗
Do you?
不记得
No.
我能原谅你
Well, I can forgive that.
昨晚简直一团糟
Last night was kind of a shitstorm.
就是我把绳子递给那些人 把你绑起来的
I was the guy that gave the rope to the guys that tied you up.
我总是带着一些绳子
I always keep some close.
用绳子能做许多有趣的事情
There's just all kinds of fun and interesting things you can do with rope.
天啊 你真漂亮
God, you're pretty.
如果我给你水喝
If I give you some water,
这是我不该做的事
which is not something I'm supposed to do,
你愿意为我做点事吗
will you do something for me?
做点你不该做的事
Something you're not supposed to do?
你愿意吗
Will you?
告诉我你有多渴
Tell me how thirsty you are.
去死吧
Go to hell.
该死
Oh, shit.
反抗只会让过程更持久
Fighting's just gonna make it last longer.
告诉你 我无所谓
Which, for the record, is fine by me.
大卫
David!
你在这里他妈干什么呢
What the hell are you doing in here?
尼根 先生
Negan, sir --
你真觉得我需要你回答吗
Do you really think I need you to answer that?
我能看出你想强奸这女人
I can see that you're trying to rape this woman.
你想强奸这女人 对吧
You were trying to rape this woman, weren't you?
这是不可接受的行为
This is some unacceptable behavior.
强奸违反了这里的规定
Rape is against the rules here.
我可不想待在允许强奸的地方
I wouldn't wanna be somewhere where it wasn't.
负责的人放过这种事…
Someone in charge who let something like that fly...
大卫
David.
你真的越线了
You really crossed a line here.
抱歉 先生
I'm sorry, sir.
知道吗
You know what?
我不接受你的道歉
I do not accept your apology.
给…
Get, uh...
萨沙
Sasha.
这名字真好听
That is a beautiful name.
给萨沙拿件新衬衫
Get Sasha here a new T-shirt.
让你看到了这些 我很抱歉
I'm sorry you had to see that.
对绳子的事我也很抱歉
Sorry 'bout the rope, too.
也许有些小题大做
Probably overkill,
但你昨晚闹了好大一场事
but you did cause one hell of a fracas last night.
该死
Oh, shit.
我记得你
I remember you.
嗯
Yeah.
你当时在场
You were there.
该死 我现在懂了
Oh, hell. I get it now.
我得承认
I got to hand it to you.
你这娘们真他妈有种
You've got some beach-ball-sized lady nuts on you,
不顾死活地就来了
coming in all kamikaze like that.
问题是
Big question here,
我需要你说实话
and I need the truth on this one --
是瑞克派你来的吗
Did Rick put you up to this?
瑞克
Rick?
你的婊子吗
Your bitch?
不是
No.
无论如何 你肯定以为你必死无疑
Either way, you must've thought it was gonna be the end,
毕竟你独自那样闯进来
coming in on your lonesome like that.
但事情不会这样发展
But that's not the way it's got to go.
恰恰相反
Unh-unh. Just the opposite.
这
See, this...
这可能只是个开始
Well, this could be the beginning.
刀现在归你了
This knife is yours now.
你可以试着使用 干掉我
You can try to use it, take me out,
但考虑到我站在你上方
but considering I am standing above you,
拿着一根棒球棒
holding a baseball bat,
那可不是明智之举
that doesn't seem real smart.
你可以用刀来割腕
Now, you can use it to slit your wrists,
这就太可惜了 但我懂
which would be a damn shame, but I get it.
考虑到最近发生的事 你显然
You're obviously not on the shiny side of the street,
不是什么阳光女人
given recent events.
你可以坐在那里 什么也不做
Now, you can sit there and do nothin',
等着老大卫复活 咬掉你的脸
wait for ol' David to come back to life and eat your face,
这也很可惜 有些疯狂
also a damn shame and kinda nuts,
但你有权做出选择
but, hell, to each their own.
或者你可以用刀来干掉强奸犯老大卫
Or you can use that blade and stop ol' Rapey Davey
阻止他变成强奸犯行尸大卫
from becoming Dead-Alive Rapey Davey,
自己救自己 加入救世军
save yourself, join the cause.
我知道我要拿你怎么办
I know what I'd do.
怎么办
What?
我少了个男丁
I'm a man short.
妈的 这个人渣其实算不上男人
Hell, you can't really call this piece of shit a man,
但依然我少了人
but still, I'm short,
而你这娘们有种极了
and you got those beach-ball-sized lady nuts,
我想要好好利用你的勇气
and I wanna harness the heat comin' off of 'em.
有朝一日你可以帮我掌管这个地方
You can help me run this place one day,
我们所有人一起 跟着规矩走
all of us together, following the rules,
站在同一战线
workin' on the same side of things.
从来都是这么回事儿
That's all this was ever about.
你也依然可以选这条路
And it still can be for you.
考虑到我的所作所为
I know it's hard to picture,
我知道你难以想象
considering what I did.
但是 萨沙 人人都有不得不迈过去的坎
But, Sasha, we all got shit to get over.
花点时间 好好想想
Take some time. Think about it.
无论你的决定如何 都由你说了算
Whatever you decide, so it shall be.
别有压力
No pressure.
还有 再次道歉 很抱歉你不得不目睹那幕
And, again, I am sorry you had to see that,
虽然我知道你是见过场面的
even though I know you have seen some things.
我只希望你能明白…
I just want you to understand...
我们不是怪物
we are not monsters.
他们把你怎么了
What did they do to you?
他们在保护我
They're keepin' me safe.
我给你带了些能让你舒服点的东西
I brought you some creature comforts.
实话说 这枕头不防过敏
Full disclosure, the pillow is not hypoallergenic.
关于我该不该过来有过一些争论
There was some debate as to whether or not I should come in here.
他们说假如我被你携刀劫持的话
They said in the event of a hostage situation with the pig sticker
我就只能靠自己了
that I would fully be on my own.
我就这么一说
Just wanted to share that.
尼根向我传达了他对你的招安之意
Negan relayed to me his offer to you.
在我看来你应该接受
It's my opinion that you should accept said offer,
就像我一样
just as I did.
我知道这是不得己而为之的情况
I know it's a hold-your-nose situation,
但与这里的头头做朋友
but taking up with the management here
真的是正确的选择
was indeed the correct select.
我曾经认为自己可以勇敢起来
You know, I believed I could be brave,
当一个亚伯拉罕那样的生存者…
that I could be a survivor like Abraham was,
开着那辆房车驶向夕阳是…
and ridin' that RV into the sunset was...
我一生中最棒的37分钟
some of the greatest 37 minutes of my existence.
但我如今明白那只是一个完全不切实际的幻想
But I know now that I was full-tilt delusional.
我这辈子最害怕的一次
I have never in my life been as scared
就是那晚在那个林子里
as I was that night in the woods,
跪在地上
kit to the grit,
觉得自己死定了
fully believing my number's about to be called,
然后看见勇敢的生存者…
then seeing it happen to someone brave...
被杀了
...to a survivor.
然后那种让人吓尿裤子的恐惧
And then the pants-pissing terror
看着那个场景一次又一次地出现…
of the rinse and repeat of that very same event --
我…
I just...
我做不到
I couldn't.
来这边意味着我再也不用恐惧了
Being here means I'll never have to again.
假如你答应的话 你也不用了
And neither will you if you just say "yes."
求求你答应吧
Please say "yes."
他希望你能答应
He would want you to.
他不希望
He wouldn't.
我希望
I do.
我们依然活着
We're still here.
世道已经变了 我们可以随之做出改变
Things have changed. We can change with 'em.
我们必须如此
We have to.
走吧
Go.
- 他已经开始…  - 拜托了
He's, uh, starting to...  Please.
走吧
Go.
我还从没见过你到墙外来昵
Don't think I've seen you outside the walls.
我建这些围墙就是为了用的
Well, I built these walls to use them.
假如我想吃绿菜了 我可以吃沙拉
If I want greenery, I eat a salad.
那你为什么来这里
Then why are you here?
我本打算找你谈谈
I was hoping we could talk.
然后我看见你一个人跑出来
Then I saw you come out here alone.
我很担心你
I was concerned.
你的朋友们呢
Where are your friends?
他们出去了
They went out.
他们在找需要的东西
They're looking for something they need.
你不去吗
Without you?
我只是好奇 你怎么还留在这 玛姬
Now, I'm just wondering -- Why you still here, Maggie?
卡森已经不在了
With Carson gone...
我听说你要救他回来
I heard you were gonna get him back.
不是吗
That not true?
还是只是说说而已
Was it just something you said?
玛姬 你得相信我
Maggie, you've got to start trusting me.
人们都很紧张 很担心
You know, people are tense, they're worried.
如果我们表现得像统一战线
Everybody'd be a hell of a lot better...
大家会感觉好得多
if we could present a-a united front.
如果我们能真正统一战线 会轻松得多
It would be a lot easier if we actually were a united front.
你说得对
You're right.
我得对合作持更开放的态度
I need to be more open to working together.
我道歉
I apologize.
我不从希望我们之间闹成这样
I never intended for things between us to come to this point.
感谢你这么说
I appreciate that.
亡羊补牢永远不算晚 知道吗
It's never too late to change. You know that?
如果你是认真的 我稍后会去找你详谈
If you're serious, I'll come by later and we can talk more.
好
Fine.
太好了
Great.
我还以为很快就能完事
I thought this'd just take a second.
弄完之前你 能帮我留意一下四周吗
Would you mind keeping an eye out while I finish up?
可以吗
Could you do that?
乐意之至
Happy to.
来了一只
We got one.
我来
I'll do it.
我是来保护孕妇的
Uh, uh...I'm here to protect the pregnant lady.
不用孕妇保护我
Don't need the pregnant lady to protect me.
你以前杀过行尸吗
Have you ever killed one before?
没杀过我就不可能站在这了
I wouldn't be here if I hadn't.
- 没事 我来吧  - 不
It's fine. I got it.  No.
天啊
Oh, Jesus.
好吧 你来
Fine. Do it.
玛姬
Maggie!
救救我
Please help me!
你没事吧
You okay?
他以前没杀过行尸
He hasn't killed one before.
正在学习
He's learning.
他跟我们可不是这么说的
That's not what he told us.
谢谢你救我
Thanks for the help.
你自己抓到的吗
Ooh. You catch that yourself?
- 那他妈当然  - 瑞秋
Shit, yeah. Rachel.
我是说 那当然
I mean, yeah.
- 我去把它清理干净  - 好
Gonna go clean it.  Okay.
别出声
Stay quiet
手放在头上
and put your hands on your head.
在村里时我们就该杀了你
We should've just killed you in the village.
你会庆幸你们没杀我的
You're gonna be glad you didn't.
你不是一个人来的 对吧
You're not alone, are you?
坐下
Sit.
你想干什么
What do you want?
我想让你坐下
I want you to sit.
你好 辛蒂
Hey, Cyndie.
你保证过的
You promised.
对 我保证过
Yeah. I did.
把手放在头上
Put your hands on your head.
我别无选择
I didn't have a choice.
你来这干什么
Why are you here?
我说了 我别无选择
I said I didn't have a choice.
但你们有 你俩都有
But you do, both of you do.
我的同伴现在就在外面
My friends are out there right now,
他们会攻占这里 希望不必开火
and they're gonna take this place, hopefully without firing a shot.
什么 你们要“攻占这里”
What? You're gonna "take this place"?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我们需要你们的枪
We need your guns.
什么
What?
我们要抵抗救世军
We're gonna fight The Saviors.
- 你们应该加入我们  - 不
You should join us.   No.
救世军杀害了你们的父亲
The Saviors killed your fathers,
兄弟 丈夫 儿子 而你们选择逃避
your brothers, husbands, sons, and you ran from them.
我以为我们铲除了他们
I thought we got rid of them.
碧翠丝说还有更多救世军 她说得对
Beatrice said there was more out there, and she was right.
他们回来了
They came back.
杀了我的朋友们
They killed my friends.
杀了我的女友
They killed my girlfriend.
接管了我们 夺走了我们的一切
They took us over. They took everything from us.
我们对救世军千依百顺
We do whatever The Saviors tell us to do,
他们以为我们还是那样 但不是
and they think we're still doing that, but we're not.
我们打算反抗
We're gonna fight them.
还有其他社区加入我们
And we have other communities beside us,
有了海边旅馆 我们就有了一支军队
and with Oceanside, we would have an army.
就这样吗
So, that's it?
“谢谢给枪 你们应该加入我们“
"Thanks for the guns. You should join us"?
如果我们联手 可以打败他们
If we fight them together, we can beat them.
我们必须试试
We have to try.
他们会赢的 塔拉 我见过 你也见过
They'll win, Tara. I've seen it. So have you.
和我们团队的首领谈谈 瑞克
Just talk to the leader of my group, Rick.
只用谈谈 我们不必占领这地方
Just talk, and we don't have to take over this place.
我们不想那样做
We don't want to.
我可以给他们信号停下
I can give them the signal to stop this,
但是你必须现在就告诉我
but you have to tell me right now.
听着 我们不只是藏在树林里
Listen. We're not just hiding in the woods.
我们在做事 我们没有放弃
We're doing something. We're not giving up.
我不想打破我的承诺 辛蒂
I didn't want to break my promise, Cyndie, okay?
但是世界可以属于好人 公正的人
But the world can belong to good people, to fair people,
只要我们有足够的勇气去尝试
if we're all just brave enough to try.
我们不是好人 也不勇敢
We are not good, and we are not brave.
你我都不是
Neither you nor me.
她是
She is.
所以我们才有现在这麻烦
That's why we're in this mess.
塔拉 如果你们拿走我们的枪
Look, Tara, if you take our guns,
还不如把我们全杀了
you might as well be killing us all.
这就是你们做的事
That's what you'll be doing.
我们应该和他们谈谈
We should talk to them.
不
No.
我们可以试着阻止这事
We can try to stop this.
不 辛蒂
No, Cyndie.
无所谓了
It doesn't matter.
没法阻止了
You can't.
走
Go! Go!
武器库
The arsenal!
趴下 快
On the ground. Now.
手抱头
Those hands -- Put them on your head.
拜托
Please.
你的人杀我的人
Your people killing my people?
炸弹在墙外面
The bombs were outside the walls.
你本可以阻止的
You could've stopped this.
我希望所有人都没事 真的
Look, I hope everyone is okay.
最好没事
I do. They better be.
起来
Stand up.
该走了
It's time to move.
我的腿
It's my legs.
站住 后退
Stop, stop. Back up. Back up.
辛蒂 别动
Cyndie, stop!
是空的 什么
It's empty. What?
没装弹
It's unloaded.
我们不是来伤人的
We didn't come here to hurt anybody.
辛蒂 给我
Cyndie, give it here.
快
Now.
娜塔尼亚 就和瑞克谈谈
Natania, just talk to Rick.
闭嘴
Shut up.
所有人蹲下
Everybody down!
手放头上
Hands on your heads.
所有人冷静
Everybody stay calm.
我们不想伤害任何人
We don't want anyone to get hurt.
别动 听我们说
Stay down and listen to what we say.
我们想让这件事尽量简单和平解决
We want this to go as simply and as peacefully as possible.
去那边蹲着 安静
Get down over there. Keep quiet.
我们搞出了很大动静
Now, we made a lot of noise.
所以我们想尽快了事 这样你们就可以派人
We want to wrap this up quick so you can send people
引开过来的行尸
to redirect anything coming this way.
塔拉说你们这片森林比较稀疏
Tara said your forests are relatively clear,
所以我们不会冒险
so we won't take any chances.
任何人都不必受伤
No one needs to get hurt.
重要的只是你们有什么 我们需要什么
This is just about what you have, what we need.
没人可以带走任何东西
Nobody's taking anything.
放了所有人
You need to let everyone go
立刻离开
and leave right now.
离开 不然她就得死
Just walk away or this one dies.
好的 我们会离开
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
但我们要带走你们的武器
But we're taking your weapons with us.
这点不变
That's not gonna change.
娜塔尼亚是吗
It's Natania, right?
放下枪
Put the gun down,
我们来谈谈我们可以改变什么
and let's talk about what we can change.
不 马上离开
No. Leave right now.
米恩琼 不要
Michonne, don't!
我们只是不想被打扰
We just wanna be left alone.
没问题 我们会离开
Yeah, we'll leave you alone.
立刻放开她
Just let go of her. Now.
不然我们就杀了你
Or we'll kill you.
我们都不想那样
None of us want that.
他们想让我们反抗救世军
They want us to fight The Saviors.
我们试过 输了 输得很惨
We tried that. We lost. Too much.
我们不会再失去任何东西了
We're not gonna lose anymore --
不管是我们的枪 还是我们的安全
not our guns, not our safety,
我们做了那么多 好不容易才来这里
not after everything we've done to get here.
我们会赢的
We're gonna win
只要有了你们的枪 无论你们帮不帮我们
with your guns, with or without your help.
娜塔尼亚 放下枪
Natania, put the gun down.
你杀了我 你也会死
You kill me, and you die.
我们的人一样会拿走枪 什么都不会变
And my people take the guns and nothing changes.
也许我们应该试一下
Maybe we should try.
祖母 住手吧
Grandma, stop.
结束了
It's over.
和他们谈谈吧 好吗
Just talk to them, okay?
还没完
It's not over!
他们都忘了
They've forgotten.
你们都忘了
You've all forgotten.
你们中有些人真的想反抗他们吗
Some of you actually want to fight them?
经历了那一切以后
After everything?
我们可以丢掉枪
We can lose our guns,
但我们也要离开这里去战斗吗
but us leaving this place to fight?
经历了那么多事以后
After everything?
我必须提醒你们
I have to remind you!
是的
Yes.
我会这样做 我会死
I am gonna do this, and then I'm gonna die.
但这就有这么重要
But it's that important.
这是你们的人生 你们所有人的
This is your life, all of you.
想想它现在是什么样的
Remember what it looks like.
想想他们以前是怎么对我们的
Remember what they did to us!
你们要看清楚
You need to see this.
睁眼好好看着
Open your eyes!
瑞克 有行尸
Rick! Walkers!
所有人起来
Everybody up!
让孩子们站到后面
Get the children behind us!
它们过来了
They're coming.
第一班 跟他们站一起
First shift, join them on the line.
拔刀 只杀行尸 只杀行尸
Knives out. Dead only. Dead only!
哪也别去
Don't go anywhere.
所有人 距离10英尺以内再开枪
Everyone, shots within 10 feet of the line.
就这样
That's it.
开枪
Now!
不 我们不会跟你们一起反抗他们
No. We're not fighting them with you.
拿着你们的枪滚
So take your damn guns and go.
你赢了
You win.
不
No.
你赢了
You win.
叫点人来 清理干净
Get some people in here. Clean this up.
怎么了
What?
你不会真的以为
You didn't actually think
我会让你留着这把刀吧
I was gonna let you keep this, did you?
在我相信你效忠之前
You still got a ways to go
你还有很长一段路要走呢
before I'll believe you're fully on board here.
一步步来嘛
Baby steps.
绝不是针对个人
It is absolutely not personal.
如果情况调过来
If the situation was reversed,
你肯定也不会相信我
I'm sure you wouldn't believe me, either.
但是
Still...
你自救的方式
the way you saved yourself,
你刚向我投降的方式
the way you surrendered to me just now --
是个很好的开始
That is a damn good start.
但是 我们还得办点事 萨沙
But we got to work on some things, Sasha.
不过我向你保证 我会尽量让过程充满乐趣
But I promise you, I will try to make it fun.
实话说了吧
Cards on the table...
一只小鸟告诉我
a little birdie told me
瑞克和你们其他的人在动歪脑筋
that Rick and the rest of your people are up to no good.
这需要改变
And, well, that needs to change,
而你要帮我改变
and you're gonna help me change it.
我们会找到一个双赢的方法
We're gonna find us a win-win.
怎么做
How?
- 你打算…  - 我会给你找些东西
What are you  Hey, I'm gonna get you some stuff
让你更舒适
to make you more comfortable,
让你体验一下我们能提供什么
let you have a taste of what it is we have to offer.
好好享受一晚
Spend the night enjoying it,
因为明天
'cause tomorrow...
是个大日子
is gonna be a big day.
凯尔
Kal!
什么事
Yeah?
我需要你开车带我去个地方
I'm gonna need you to drive me somewhere.
你最好打个包
You're gonna want to pack a bag.
在吗
Hello?
我是尤金
It's Eugene.
听说你愿意加入这里了
Word in the halls is that you're all-in with things here.
现在也许看起来不像
It may not seem like it now,
但是我向你保证
but I assure you,
你同样做了正确的选择
you, too, made the correct select.
我错了
I was wrong.
我做不到
I can't.
我不会做
I won't.
我一直坐在这里
I've been sitting here,
想着我怎么能做到
trying to figure out how I could,
发生了那么多事
with what happened,
我们的朋友们还在外面
with our friends still out there,
还在被他们伤害着
still being hurt by them.
我不知道我怎么能那样说
I don't know how I could've said that.
现在 我陷入了绝境
And now...I am trapped.
你必须帮我
You have to help me.
我会的
I will.
我会帮你习惯现状
I'll help you get used to the idea
阐明利害 演示为什么…
and illustrate the equation and demonstrate why
那是个错误
It was a mistake.
我本来准备好了
I was ready.
我知道如果我昨晚没杀死他
I knew, if I didn't kill him last night,
我就完了
it'd be over.
我没杀死他 所以就这样吧
And I didn't, so it is.
必须这样
It has to be.
你必须给我搞些东西来
You have to get me something --
刀 枪 剃须刀片
a knife, a gun, a razor blade.
为了尼根吗
For Negan?
不
No!
不管怎样 他都会利用我伤害我的朋友们
One way or another, he is gonna use me to hurt my friends --
我们的朋友们
our friends.
而我对此无能为力
And there is nothing I can do about it
除非我死了 不给他机会
except make sure I'm not alive to give him the chance.
只要我被活捉 他就会伤害他们
If he has me, he will hurt them.
我必须死
I have to die.
这是唯一的办法
It's the only way.
我不认为…
I-I don't  I-I don't think that
我知道你不会做任何事阻止他们
I know you won't do anything to stop them.
我知道
I know that.
但是求你了 尤金
But, please, Eugene...
别让他们利用我伤害我们的人
don't let them use me to hurt our people.
求你了 你必须给我
Please, you have to give me
一些东西了断自己 枪 刀 玻璃
something to stop this -- a gun, a knife, glass.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我必须死
I have to die.
求你了
Please.
我…
I...
我会考虑
I will consider it.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们不需要全拿走吧
We don't need all this, do we?
我们需要
Yeah. Yeah, we do.
不只是我杀的人
It's not just the ones I killed.
我也会想起我没杀的人
I think about the people I didn't kill, too.
结束后我们会把枪送回来
We're gonna bring them back when it's all over.
我想跟你们走
I-I want to go with you.
我们有些人想反抗 但不是所有人
Some of us do, but not all of us,
必须达成共识 她们才会去
and it has to be all of us.
我祖母认为你们都会死
My grandmother thinks you'll all be dead.
你祖母很多想法都是错的
Yeah, well, your grandmother's wrong about a lot of things.
她人呢
Where is she?
她不想看见这个
She didn't want to see this.
她躺下了 我把她打得挺重
She's lying down. I hit her pretty hard.
感谢你之前救我命
Thanks for saving my life before.
还有另一次
And the other time.
Oh, and then the other time.
也许今天也是
Maybe today.
谢谢
Thanks.
Thank you.
你所做的事
For what you're doing.
不给我们留一把枪吗
You're not leaving us any?
不留 回见 瑞秋
Nope. See ya later, Rachel.
你还好吧
You okay?
还好
Yeah.
你说得对
You're right.
我不必内疚
I don't have to feel bad.
萨沙
Sasha?
我在
I'm here.
我仔细权衡考虑了上次谈话
I've given our last exchange a good, hard pro/con think.
我决定满足你的请求
I've decided to grant your request.
用这个就行
This will do it.
这是毒药 本人亲手所做
It's a poison, homemade by yours truly.
摄入后20至
It will bring about certain death
30分钟内
in approximately 20 to 30 minutes
必死
upon the moment of ingestion.
我相信应该是无痛的
I would like to believe that it's painless.
我不太确定
I am not  I'm not certain.
我做这个药是因为曾有人提过类似请求
I made it at the behest of others for similar reasons,
后来我发现她们给了我虚假信息
only it came to pass that they were feeding me the bum's steer,
于是我悬崖勒马
so I cut bait.
现在的不同之处是
The difference here is that
我们俩是长期旅伴
you and I have been long-time traveling companions,
你证明了自己是一个诚实勇敢
and you have proven yourself to be honest, brave,
具备完全自我意识的人
and fully self-aware.
我确信我欠你人情
I'm certain I owe you for things.
你让我帮你找解脱办法
You asked me for a way out.
我找到了一个
I had access to one.
首先声明 我完全不希望你死
For the record, I absolutely do not want you to go.
但是听起来你已经下了必死之心
But it sounds to me like you happen to be already gone.
你没事吧
Hey, are you okay?
萨沙在哪
Where's Sasha?
有人来了
There's someone here.
慢点 等等
Slow down. Come on. Whoa!
他说他想帮我们
He says he wants to help us.
是真的吗
That true?
你想帮忙
You want to help?
是的
I do.
好
Okay.
跪下
Get on your knees.